Paul Bamidele

E: <u>bamidelepaul970@gmail.com</u> | L: <u>LinkedIn</u>

Bio

A product manager with 2 years of professional experience in managing teams and resources between businesses and customer relations and products.

Skills

- Copywriting
- Email marketing
- Time management
- Technology proficiency: CRM systems, Digital Tools like JIRA.

Career History

NFT-Factory – *Product Manager*

September 2023 – October 2024

Key responsibilities

- Liaised with board members and stakeholders to discuss budgetary and operational needs and goals resulting in 50% increase in budget.
- Reported on departmental challenges and collaborated with cross-functional teams to mitigate friction by 98%.
- Negotiated contracts with clients, influencers, and ambassadors, resulting in mutually favourable partnerships and increased growth, generating over \$10,000 in seed funding for the product.
- Developed strategy for social media marketing with cohesive messaging across multiple platforms and a 38% increase in conversion rate within six months.
- Oversaw development and execution of multi-channel marketing campaigns to drive growth by 70%.

The Blockchain Solutions (TBS) – Business Development Manager July 2023 - Present

Key responsibilities

- Drew on understanding of key markets to push development of business strategies by 10%.
- Generated leads to bring in new client revenue and improve bottom-line profitability which resulted in 30% increase in profitability.
- Maintained client records in bespoke CRM systems, ensuring streamlined data processes for maximum efficiency.
- Contacted and converted over 60% of potential customers via telephone, email and inperson enquiries.

Key responsibilities

- Tracked competitor activity, aiming to consistently be one step ahead in innovative, and captivating contents.
- Utilised communication skills to proactively identify, engage and grow users of over 10.000 users.
- Observed online trends and patterns to effectively plan future content for maximum impact.
- Created engaging content based on relevant, current topics, increasing user interaction by 40%.
- Responded to comments, messages and feedback to build the brand activity profiles, leading to user satisfaction rating of 84% and generating positive and word-of-mouth referrals.

Bit-Shore Enterprise, Nigeria – Growth Marketer September 2019 – August 2020

Key responsibilities

- Created digital and print collateral for distribution to potential clients and website markets, gathering customer insight data to inform product development and marketing content.
- Liaised with management teams in developing marketing strategies and plans to increase engagement by 20%.
- Implemented strategies to engage and attract customers, increasing brand engagement by 20% and sales by 15%.
- Oversaw email marketing campaigns using Mailchimp, optimizing content and delivery for maximum impact.

Education & qualifications

- ➤ Bachelor's Degree Obafemi Awolowo University
- ➤ Pendo's Certification in Product Management and Product Experience
- **Coursera Certification in Product Management**